人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    红豆包    奈奈良
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：今       后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第十三集
情人节快乐  我亲爱的家人们
Happy Valentine's Day to all my loves.
亲亲脸蛋  大家都有份
Smooches. Everyone gets a smooch.
我的那份给吉恩吧
Oh, give Gene mine.
亲我吧
I'll take it.
希望我老婆准备好迎接浪漫惊喜了
I hope a certain wife is ready to be romanced.
鲍鲍
Oh, Bobby.
心形的薄饼
A pancake shaped like a heart.
残次品都给我们了
We got the rejects.
我的薄饼像片胡须
Mine's like a moustache.
薄饼之旅  五美分一人
Pancake rides, five cents.
我看不到我的长什么样子
I can't see what mine looks like,
不过摸起来像只耳朵
but it feels ear-shaped maybe?
你在桌子底下干什么呢  你个小傻蛋
What are you doing under the table, you silly.
假装不在
Hiding.
因为如果我人不在的话
I mean I'm not here
就不能去学校了
so I can't go to school.
但今天是情人节啊
But it's Valentine's day.
你很喜欢情人节的
You love Valentine's day.
那是在去年的情人节灾难之前
Until the St. Valentine's Day disaster last year.
什么
What?
我说的是小吉米的情人节卡片
I'm talking about Jimmy Jr.'s Valentine card.
送你的  蒂娜
Here, Tina.
"来自于"?
"From"?
不
No!
"来自于"这个词已让我心如死灰
My heart was murdered by the word of 'from'.
没人说我"来自于"你[我爱你]
No one says "I from you."
我今天不去上学了
I'm not going to school today.
如果蒂娜不去  我也不去了
If Tina's not going, I'm not going.
过去点
Scoot over.
没错  我们有协议的
Yeah, we made a pact.
所有人都给我出来
Everybody out from under there.
上学去
You're all going to school.
-不去  -得去
- No. - Yes.
在这下面也能学到很多东西呢
There's a lot of learning to do down here.
下面有什么
What's under there?
要不要下来看看
Wouldn't you like to know?
快点  下雨了  我开车送你们去学校
Come on, it's raining, I'll give you a ride.
系好安全带  系好安全带
Buckle it up, buckle it up
系好安全带  否则小命不保
Buckle it up or you'll die.
怎么样  我今年是不是让你们老妈
So? I'd say I knocked it out of the park
大吃了一惊
with your mother this year.
更像是挥了拳却什么也没打重
Mm, more like a swing and a miss.
心形薄饼简直和"来自于"一样糟
Heart-shaped pancakes is just as bad as a "From."
不  才不是
No, it isn't.
你每年做的事情都千篇一律  老爸
You do the same thing every year, Dad.
-你得搞些花样  -没错
- You need to mix it up. - Yeah.
啥  我搞花样了啊
What? I mixd it up.
虽然我总是在"心"上做文章
I mean, I stick to a central theme, hearts,
可你们老妈很吃这一套
but your mom loves them.
是的  她向来乐此不疲
Yeah, she never gets tired of them.
怎么样
Well?
成熟点吧  老爸
Grow up, Dad.
只有孩子才送手制的礼物
Only kids get to make homemade gifts.
她今年该收份体面的礼物了
She deserves something nice this year.
娶到老妈可是你的福气
Mom's a real keeper.
还好啦
She's okay.
琳  今年鲍勃又在最后时刻
So, Lin, did Bob make another last-minute
做了心形的东西吗
heart-shaped thing this year?
薄饼
Flapjacks.
没关系啦
Ah, it's all right.
礼物并不重要
Valentine's Day isn't about valentines.
重要的是两个人彼此相爱
It's about two people being in love.
*两个人*
*Two people*
*永远在一起*
*Together forever*
*安稳的生活*
*Security in life*
*有人爱你*
*And someone to love ya*
*不再孤单*
*Instead of being all alone*
*如果这样孤独的活着*
*Such a lonely existence*
*我宁愿去死*
*I'd kill myself.*
这歌真心酸
Tough song.
在唱我们俩呢  莫特
It's talking about us, Mort.
天哪  真抱歉
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
就我自己在这唧唧歪歪  都没想到你们
Going on about love when you guys don't...
根本没体验过被爱的滋味么
Have any love... in the slightest?
我有一个很棒的主意
I just got a great idea.
我今天要帮你们俩个都找到爱情
I'm gonna find love for both of you today.
我们来个快速约会
We are gonna do speed dating.
-很好  我要参加  -我也参加
- All right. I could go for that. - I'm in.
我来做个告示
I'll make a sign.
一定很有趣
Oh, this is gonna be fun.
好吧  你们觉得你们老妈想要什么
Okay, so what do you think your mom wants--
巧克力还是香水
chocolates? Perfume?
我们根本不必猜
We don't think what Mom wants.
我们很清楚她想要什么
We know what Mom wants.
太好了  她想要什么
Great, what does she want?
小型陶瓷雕像
A Grazielda figurine.
对哦  那些瓷做的小玩意儿
Oh, yeah, those porcelain thingies.
好吧  我会去买一个的  谢了
Okay, I'll-I'll get one of those. Thanks.
好吧  祝你们今天过得愉快  孩子们
All right, have a good day, kids.
老爸  有上百种  甚至上千种雕像
Dad, there are hundreds of Grazieldas, thousands maybe.
她们抢了我们的工作  还娶了我们的女人
Taking our jobs, marrying our women.
只有我们知道老妈想要哪一款
Only we know the exact one Mom wants.
没错  如果选错了款式  相当于没送
Yeah, if you pick the wrong one, it's like you got her nothing!
好吧  那你们告诉我  到底是哪一款
Okay, so tell me -- which one is it?
我们会告诉你的  不过得等到了商场
We'll tell you... at the mall.
对  我们应该去商场
Yeah, we should go to the mall.
在那儿我的心就不会被小吉米摧残了
My heart will be safe from Jimmy Jr. there.
我才不会带你们逃课去逛商场
Hey, I'm not taking you out of school to go to the mall.
好吧  反正这是你的婚姻
Okay, well, you know, it's your marriage.
你挡住道了
You're holding up the line.
等一下  马上就好
Hold on, one minute.
我真想冲她吼两嗓子
Hmm, I could stand to wow her.
那就吼吧
Then wow the woman.
-别摁了  等一下  -快开走
- Stop, I'm... wait! - Come on, move it!
你起开
You move it!
我在和我的孩子们道别
I'm saying good-bye to my kids!
-你确定你知道吗  -我知道
- You're sure you know? - I know.
好吧  那我们就去商场
All right, we're going to the mall then!
去商场  好耶
To the mall! Yeah!
吃屎去吧  蠢货
Eat it, you losers!
系好安全带  系好安全带
Buckle it up, buckle it up
系好安全带  否则小命呜呼
Buckle it up or you'll die.
我的妈呀商场
好了  我们进去后你们告诉我买哪一款
Okay, we go in, you tell me which one to buy,
我十点前送你们回学校
I get you back to school by 10:00,
你们可以告诉你们的老师  你们
and you can tell your teachers, um, you had, uh...
有阅读障碍
A dyslexic episode!
怀孕了
Pregnancy.
得疱疹了
Shingles.
对  很好  就这样
Uh, yeah, that's good, fine.
怎么感觉都很土啊
Wow, these are all so corny.
撑伞的小狗怎么会土呢
What's so corny about a puppy under an umbrella?
好吧  你们老妈想要哪一个
All right, so which one does your mom want?
-那个  -那个
- That one! - That one!
-那个吗  -那个
- That one? - That one.
等等  你们根本就不知道
Wait a second, you have no clue
她想要哪一个
which one your mom wants.
你们是在骗我好让我带你们逃学
You just tricked me to get out of school.
好大的胆子
How dare you!
我也被他们骗了  老爸
I believed them, too, Dad.
真够难堪的啊
Egg on our face, huh?
我猜你是来给你可爱的妻子选礼物的吧
Let me guess -- looking for a Grazielda for your lovely wife?
是的  哪一个最便宜
Yeah, so which one is the least expensive?
这是我们最基本的一款  叫小贵妇
Oh, this is kind of our starter figurine-- La Princessa.
价值250美金
She's $250.
什么  这还是最便宜的
What? That's your cheapest?
我不喜欢你这么说
I don't like that word.
也许你和你的妻子都不是忠实粉丝
Perhaps you nor your wife are really serious about Grazieldas.
不  我们不是
No, we're not.
谁会对这些东西认真
Who would be serious about these things?
比尔・贝利奇克  彼得・佛莱普顿
Bill Belichick, Peter Frampton,
前者为美国橄榄球队教练  后者为英国摇滚乐手
琳达・朗雯  我还可以说出更多
Linda Lavin to name a few.
美国歌手兼演员
孩子们  我们走了
Kids, we're leaving.
快速约会  菜好得快  爱来得也快
女士们  欢迎参加开心汉堡店快速约会
Welcome, ladies, to Bob's Burgers' Speed Dating.
你们和在座的绅士们有一分钟的交谈时间
You'll have one minute with these fine gentlemen,
当你们听到这个时
and when you hear this,
请交换约会伙伴
switch partners.
但如果你听到这个
But if you hear this,
请交换话题
change topics.
大家都准备好坠入爱河了吗
And who's ready to fall in love?
快速约会开始
Speed date.
泰迪  这位是吉娜
So, Teddy, this is Gina.
你们即将坠入爱河
You two are now in pre-love.
-是吗  -你们有一分钟的时间搞清楚
- We are? - Well, you got 60 seconds to figure it out.
时间不等人  开始吧
So, ticktock, let's go.
我是泰迪
Uh, I'm Teddy,
刚才琳达已经介绍过了
like Linda said earlier.
我们谈点什么呢
Um, what do we talk about?
-我不知道  -我们谈点什么
- Uh, I don't know. - What do we talk about?
我想像舔信封一样舔它
I want to lick this one like an envelope, mmm.
很好  邮递员玩笑
Great, mail jokes.
原来你是邮递员啊
Oh, you're a mailman.
孩子们  这个手机壳怎么样
Kids, how about this cell phone cover?
上面写着  "我是熟女"
It says, "Got Milf."
很棒的礼物  对吧  可以送你们老妈
That's perfect, right? For your mom?
我就买它了  然后送你们回学校
I'll get this and then I'll bring you kids back to school.
学校  别操之过急嘛
School? Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
老爸  你得给她惊喜
Dad, you need to wow her.
这玩意可不能给她惊喜
This is not gonna wow her.
你怎么还是这么敷衍  老爸
I thought you were done half-assing it, Dad.
你就不能再浪漫一点么
Why can't you be more romantic?
啥  我可浪漫了
What? I'm plenty romantic.
-真可笑  -别傻了
- Very funny. - Stop goofing.
你为老妈做过的最浪漫的事是什么
What was the most romantic thing you ever did for Mom?
我不知道  我有计划
I don't know, I planned stuff.
有一次我为她计划了整整一天的浪漫惊喜
I planned a whole romantic day one time.
那是在她的生日
It was her birthday...
不对  等等  那是我的生日
No, wait, it was my birthday...
不不不  等等  那天是情人节
No, no, no, wait, it was Valentine's Day.
那是我们一起过的第一个情人节
It was our first Valentine's Day together.
你太不会讲故事了
You are the worst storyteller.
你的口才灵感都跑哪儿去了
Where's Maya Angelou when you need him?
我准备了野餐篮  载她去看夕阳
Yeah, I made a picnic basket and I picked out a spot
后来我的汽车出故障了
to watch the sunset, and then my car died.
于是我们让人把车拖去了修车厂
So we had to get towed to the mechanic's.
请务必告诉我车到底出了什么毛病
Tell me exactly what was wrong with the car.
是垫圈的问题吗
Was it a gasket?
是汽化器的问题吗
Was it the carburetor?
各位  他在跟我们讲一个浪漫的故事
Guys, he's telling us a romantic story.
汽车送去修理的期间
While the car was getting fixed,
我们去了街对面的酒吧
we went to a bar across the street.
那里没有海边的夕阳
It wasn't the beach at sunset,
但我们玩得很开心
but we, uh, we had a great time.
那儿有一台类似测爱仪之类的旧机器
And there was this old beat-up machine, like a love tester
我们一起推了操控杆
or something,and we squeezed the lever together,
机器显示我们正处于狂热阶段
and it said we were "Red hot."
然后她亲了我
And she kissed me and
就是在那一刻  我知道我们恋爱了
that's, uh, that's when I knew we were in love.
就是它了  给老妈买那个测爱仪
That's it. Buy Mom the love tester.
什么意思  买那台机器本人吗
What do you mean, the actual machine?
没错  那样她一定会嫁给你的
Yeah, she'd totally marry you if you did that.
老爸  你还记得那个酒吧在哪儿吗
Dad, do you remember where that bar is?
要花上一天的时间去找吗
Will it take all day to find it?
我想我还记得它的位置
Hmm, I do think I remember where it is.
真的吗  我们有任务了
Oh, really? We've got a mission.
最伟大的任务
The most noble mission there is --
爱的任务
a love mission.
传教士体位[男上女下的性交姿势]任务
It's a missionary position mission.
搞不好她真的会喜欢
Yeah, she'd really like that.
也许最多花得了五十块
Probably get it for, like, 50 bucks, tops.
好了  我送你们去学校
All right, I'll drop you off at school
然后我去潜水酒吧
and then I'll go to the dive bar.
你在想什么
That's crazy.
还去什么学校啊
School is way out of the way.
那条单行道在施工
They're doing construction on that one street,
又下着雨  肯定堵得要命
it's raining -- what a clusterjam.
老爸  我们得和你一起去
We should go with you, Dad.
好吧  那就先一起去  然后马上回
All right, you can come, but then right back to...
我不想再听到学校这个词
Uh-uh-uh, not another word about school.
去潜水酒吧咯
To the dive bar!
下一项约会游戏
Next dating game...
速配牵手
speed hand holding.
好了  开始
And... hold hands.
泰迪  泰迪
Teddy, Teddy,
你要伤到她了
you're gonna hurt her.
不是叫你压扁她
You're not trying to crush her.
-啥  -我不介意的
- What? - I don't mind it rough.
非常好  莫特
Very good, Mort.
你太温柔了
You are as limp as can be.
温温的黏黏的  这是我的招牌牵手方式
Limp and clammy, my signature hold.
博斯柯探长
Sergeant Bosco!
有何贵干
What are you doing here?
前街的一家珠宝店被抢了
Someone just robbed a jewelry store on Front Street.
劫匪往这边逃了
He fled on foot in this direction
我们正挨家挨户的搜查
so we're going door-to-door.
我们掌握的线索只有
Oh. All we know is he's
他高约1米78到1米83  体格健壮
five-ten to six-feet tall with an athletic build.
很明显你们没人符合
Eh, none of you guys fit that description.
-真伤人  -好汉不提当年勇
- That's harsh. - A few years ago.
博斯柯  我不禁注意到  你没戴婚戒
Bosco, I couldn't help notice you don't have a wedding ring.
难道也被偷了吗
Did the guy steal that, too?
没有  戒指在我离婚后
No, I chucked it into a ravine
就被我扔进山谷里了
after my divorce went through.
500街没发现异常
500 block is negative.
继续找
Well, keep looking!
妈的  本来都快抓到他
Damn, we had him,
又被他溜了
and then we lost him.
-博斯柯你在跟我说话吗  -不是
- Talking to me, Bosco? - No!
那麻烦你别按着讲话键不放
Maybe don't leave your thumb on the button?
这里是怎么回事
Eh, what's going on in here?
快速约会
Speed dating.
美女们  又新来了位参赛者
Ladies, I think we've got a new contestant.
不了  我要真想自取其辱
No, no, if I wanted to feel like a loser,
就跟我孩子打电话了
I'd just call my kids.
但这是开心汉堡店的快速约会
But this is Bob's Burgers' Speed Dating.
美女和警察就餐免费
Ladies and cops eat free.
好吧  就在你这待五分钟
All right, you got five minutes.
速配起来
Okay, couple up!
有什么能帮您的
How can I help you?
大约15年前我来这
Yeah, I was here about 15 years ago
玩了一个老旧的类似测爱仪一样的东西
and I-I played this old timey-looking love tester thing.
你还留着它吗
Do you still have it?
你是说恋爱博士测爱仪吗
You mean Dr. Love's Love Testometer?
对  就是那个
Yeah, that's it.
他知道  太棒了
He knows it. Hooray.
老板几年前卖掉了
Eh, the owner sold it a few years ago.
天哪
Oh, man.
你知道他卖给谁了吗
Do you know who he sold it to?
抱歉  不太清楚
Nah, no clue, sorry.
我知道它在哪
I know where it is.
-雨果  -鲍勃
- Hugo! - Bob.
-鲍勃  -罗恩
- Bob. - Ron.
-雨果  -怎么了
- Hugo. - Yes, what?
你知道这的那个原本在这儿的测爱仪
Oh. You know where the love testometer
现在在哪吗
that used to be here is?
知道  事实上今天晚些时候
I do. In fact, later today I'm inspecting
我还会去那家店进行考察
the establishment where it's currently testometering.
太好了
That's great.
我觉得你与其买古董玩意儿
I think you should invest in new soap
还不如花钱把卫生间的肥皂换一换
for your bathroom before you purchase vintage amusements.
你以为我们卫生间只有肥皂是问题吗
You think soap's the problem with our bathroom?
可这不是给餐馆买的
But it's not for the restaurant.
是我要送琳达的情人节礼物
It's my Valentine's Day gift for Linda.
哎呀  我刚忘记在哪了
Oops, I just forgot where it is.
别闹了
Oh, come on.
我才不会帮你给琳达
I'm not helping you buy Linda
买浪漫的情人节礼物
a romantic Valentine's gift.
雨果  也许你该告诉他
Maybe you should tell him, Hugo.
也许我不想听这种话  罗恩
Maybe I don't want to hear it, Ron.
好吧
All right.
你真是个混蛋  雨果
You're such a jerk, Hugo, you know that?
在我管辖范围内有
There are 97 bars and restaurants
97家酒吧和餐馆
in my expansive jurisdiction.
慢慢找去吧  鲍勃
Good luck finding it, Bob.
还是回商场吧
Back to the mall, I guess.
老爸  别就这么退缩
Don't take this lying down, Dad.
但是雨果不告诉我测爱仪在哪儿
But Hugo won't tell us where the testometer is.
他说了今天会去那家店考察的
He said he's inspecting the place today.
也就是说  是哪一天来着
So, okay, so what day is it?
-就是今天啊  -是的
- It's today. - Right.
所以你跟着他就行了
So you have to follow him.
对极了
Yes!
这可是情人节  拜托
It's Valentine's Day, damn it.
你说得对  他会带我们找到测爱仪的
You're right. He'll lead us right to the love testometer.
-开车咯  -好呀
- Let's ride. - Hyah!
但最好先来杯热巧克力什么的
But let's get a hot chocolate or something first.
外面在下雨呢
It's all rainy out.
好主意  尤金[吉恩大名]
Great idea, Eugene.
跟太近了  他会发现的
You're too close! He'll see us.
我心里有数
I know what I'm doing.
中间有辆车挡着呢
I've got a buffer car.
他就快带我们找到测爱仪了
You're gonna lead us right to the testometer.
跟丢了
And... we lost him.
还没有  我们会跟上的
We didn't lose him, we'll catch up.
我还看得见他的车
I can still see him.
他拐弯了
Look, he's turning.
别别  别拐弯
No, no, no, don't turn.
好吧
All right, uh...
来看看能否神不知鬼不觉地闯个红灯
Let's see if I can safely go through this red light.
要跟丢了  开车啊  很安全的
We're losing him. Drive! It's safe! It's safe!
对不起
Oh, sorry.
对不  我就走
Sorr... I'll go.
我要拐  停车
I'll go... Stop!
好吧
Okay!
我是  我是联邦调查局的
I'm... I'm in the FBI.
这是  在执行公务
It's ... it's official business!
抱歉
S-sorry.
好  新游戏
All right, new game.
大家来说最爱吃的食物
Everyone say your favorite food.
开始
Go.
酱油
Soy sauce.
蜡唇[俚语  意指满嘴大话的人]
Wax lips?
白米饭
Plain white rice.
油炸绿蕃茄
Fried green tomatoes.
最爱的做爱姿势  开始
Favorite love-making position. Go!
观音坐莲[油炸绿蕃茄]
The Fried Green Tomato.
颠鸾倒凤
The Pick n' Roll.
吟猿抱树
The Broken Sprinkler.
鱼翔浅底
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang.
貂禅拜月
The Sticky Wicket.
不对不对  让他们说最喜欢的事情
No, no, no. Getting people to say their favorite things
不管用的
isn't gonna work.
当然管用
Sure it is.
如果你们爱吃的东西
If you like the same food
做爱的姿势都一样  就是潜在发展对象
or sex angles, you're compatible.
我和你看法完全相反
I'd do the exact opposite.
我会让他们说出自己最坏的一面
I'd make everyone say the worst thing about themselves,
最尴尬见不得人的阴暗面
the most embarrassing, darkest secret.
如果对方还能忍受得了你
If the other person can stomach you for another second,
那也许你们会成为恋人  也许而已
then maybe you have a chance together, maybe.
什么  那也太不浪漫了
What? That is the least romantic...
我想要玩那个
I want to do it.
玩吧
Let's do it.
我同意
I'm game.
不
No.
我先来
I'll go first.
我其实是帮会组织的成员
Hi there. I'm part of a secret society.
我们抓罪犯只是为了娱乐
We hunt men for sport.
到我了  我感染宫颈十年了
Hello. I've had a yeast infection for ten years.
打住  吉娜  别说了
Stop. Oh, Gina, no.
有时我会把信件丢到下水道
Sometimes I just put the mail down the storm drain.
我就知道  我就知道
I knew it. I knew it.
你总算说出来了
Yeah, there you go.
我曾经谎报有炸弹威胁
I called in a bomb threat once
因为我听说马克・汉蒙住那家宾馆
'cause I heard Mark Harmon was staying at this hotel.
美国男演员
我想等他被疏散出来
I wanted to see him evacuate,
然后就趁机跟踪他个一年半载的
and then I stalked him for a year
再开车撞死他老婆
and hit his wife with my car.
别说了
No, stop it.
坦白自己的黑暗面
Saying icky stuff about yourselves
根本不是情人节的宗旨
isn't what Valentine's Day is about.
都别说了
Now, stop it.
这就是爱情的本来面目
Well, it's what love's about.
如果你们女人能搬动我的行李
And if you women can handle my baggage,
那么你可以跟我一同乘机
then you can fly with me,
但请自己备好呕吐袋
but bring a sick bag,
因为旅途注定颠簸崎岖
'cause it's gonna be a real bumpy ride.
等等  内裤湿了
Clean-up, aisle my panties.
不
No.
-喂  过来  -干嘛
- Psst, over here. - Huh?
你这儿有没有一台投硬币的
Hey, do you have a coin-operated machine
可以预测爱情的机器
in there that predicts love?
怎么每次出来扔垃圾
Can't I just take out the trash
都能被变态搭讪
one time without getting hit on by some perv?
就算是变态  他也是我老爸
He may be a perv, but that's my dad.
雨果不知道还要等多久
Hugo's gonna take forever.
为什么非要等雨果
We wouldn't have to wait for Hugo
带我们去下一家呢
to lead us to the next place
提前知道他的路线不就行了
if we found out where he's going.
墨西哥卷小屋
锁住了
It's locked.
但是窗户开了个缝
But the window's open a crack.
也许我们能找个衣架或是
Maybe we can find a hanger or...
衣架是用来挂去主日学校穿的衣服的
Hangers are for Sunday school clothes.
主日学校: 教堂在星期日对儿童进行基督教教育的课堂
我去拿石头
Bring me a rock.
我们不能砸玻璃
We're not smashing the window.
我们可以假装是下雨下的
It'll look like the rain did it.
快点  拿到那个记事本
Do it. Get that clipboard.
-吉恩  住手  -谢谢
- Gene, stop. - Uh, thanks.
要不然雨果会怪我的
Hugo would have blamed me for that.
你好啊
Oh, hey.
罗恩你好
Hi, Ron.
这是...
This is...
罗恩  你在这干嘛呢
Ron, what are you doing here? Hey!
这不是我的车
This not my van.
我们就是想
We were just gonna
从这车里买点冰激凌
get some ice cream from this truck here.
我们只是想拿那个记事本
We're just getting the clipboard.
雨果不帮你是他不对
Listen, Hugo's wrong not to help you out.
虽然我不知道哪家有那个测爱仪
I don't know which place has the testometer,
不过  这是我们今天要考察店面的详单
but, uh, this is where we're going today.
谢谢你  罗恩
Hey, thanks, Ron.
我们会一家家排查的
You know, we'll check those places out.
你这样帮我们  真是个好人
You're a good guy to help us.
是个大大的好人
You're a great guy.
我对你另眼相看了
I look up to you, man. Oh.
我不介意多交一个你这样的朋友
I wouldn't mind having a friend like you.
好  走吧  孩子们
Okay, let's go, kids.
再次谢谢你  罗恩
Thanks again, Ron.
回见
See you.
沙拉饼干三明治
*沙拉三明治*
*Falafel*
*我们在执行爱的任务*
*We're on a love mission*
沙拉饼干三明治  啪啪披萨
饮者湾  印度香  尾楼甲板
*披萨*
*Pizza*
*我们在执行爱情任务*
*We're on a love mission*
*剩下的几家*
*All the rest*
*我们在执行爱情任务*
*We're on a love mission*
单身汉酒吧
孩子们  待在外面
Kids, uh, stay outside.
打扰了各位  你们有测爱仪这种东西吗
Excuse me, sir, do you have something called the love testometer?
测爱仪在这呢  伙计
I got your love testometer right here, pal.
这一幕我得存脑子里
That goes in the buttbank.
这是单子上最后一处了
Well, this is the last place on the list.
最好能在这
It better be here.
龙朝豪饮
我要一杯"七和七"[鸡尾酒名称]
I'll have a seven and seven.
不  帮我做杯"八和八"好了
No! Make it an eight and eight.
我的要加倍
Make mine a double, would you?
"十六和十六"  谢了
A 16 and 16, thank you.
给我来白开水就好
I'm good with water.
不  等等  白开水就好
No, wait. Um, yeah, just water.
孩子们  适可而止
Kids, please.
我找了好大一圈
Look, I-I've been driving all over,
就是为了给我妻子准备情人节礼物
trying to find my wife this Valentine's gift,
你是我最后的希望
and you're my last hope.
这些迷你雨伞很受欢迎
Everybody loves these tiny umbrellas.
她想要多少个
How many does she want?
不不不  我要找的是
No, no, no. I'm actually looking
恋爱博士测爱仪
for Dr. Love's Love Testometer.
你可一定要有啊  我想从你那儿买
Please say you have it; I want to buy it from you.
你要买我的测爱仪
You want to buy my love testometer?
你  你真的有吗
You-you actually have it?
就在那边
Yeah, it's right over there.
跟我记忆中的一模一样
It's exactly as I remembered.
好美
It's beautiful.
-我很乐意把它卖给你  -太好了
- I'd love to sell it to you. - Great!
但我不能  因为我已经把它卖掉了
But I can't, I already sold it.
你好呀  鲍勃
Hello, Bob.
看看人家刚买了虾米
Lookie what I just boughtie.
遇到你真巧呀  鲍勃
Odd bumping into you here, Bob.
等等  不  不对
Oh, wait. No, it's not.
我知道你会来这儿
I knew you were coming, thanks to
这要多亏这位给谁都开车门的先生
Mr. Opens-the-van-for-anyone over here.
雨果发现他的记事本少了一页
Hugo noticed the missing carbon copy from the clipboard.
书呆子一个
Nerd.
以后禁止罗恩跟我坐前排
Now Ron's not allowed to ride up front with me in the van.
快点  老爸  你要为老妈拿到测爱仪
Come on, Dad, you need to get that testometer for Mom.
我就快消失了
I'm starting to disappear.
他花多少买了那个
How much did he pay for that?
-那破玩意就卖了100块  -好吧
- A hundred bucks for that junk. - All right.
雨果  求你把测爱仪卖给我
Hugo, please sell me the love testometer.
-不要  -雨果  这无关我俩的恩怨
- Uh, no. - Hugo, this isn't about me and you.
而是关系着一个女人能否得到像样的礼物
This is about giving a woman a gift
来弥补她多年来的...
to make up for years of-of...
-垃圾人生  -也不能这么说  蒂娜
- Crap? - Well, not quite crap, Tina.
-毫无惊喜的人生  -垃圾人生
- Last-minute nothings? - Crap.
雨果  拜托了  把它卖给我
Listen, Hugo, please sell it to me.
这是琳达该得的
Linda deserves it.
行  鲍勃  我卖给你
Okay, Bob, I will sell it to you.
500块
For $500.
可你只花了100块啊
But you only paid $100.
500块  那东西是有魔力还是怎么的
$500? Is that thing magic?
你爱要不要吧  鲍勃
You want it or not, Bob?
他当然要啦
Of course he wants it.
只是他的钱这会儿全套房地产了
It's just his money's all tied up in real estate right now so...
你接受假信用卡吗
Do you take fake credit cards?
好吧  我买了
All right, fine.
再告诉你一件事  我有药瘾
Another thing about me, I'm hooked on pills.
那种能让你嗨的不好的药
The bad kind that make you feel good.
我喜欢玩溜溜球
I like to play with a yo-yo,
我感觉这样总有东西会回到我身边
so something comes back to me.
各位  坦白就到此结束吧
People, enough with the confessions.
其实  这块地毯下可是地中海哦
You should know that there's hardwood under this carpet.
干得漂亮
Yeah, there you go.
别这样  莫特  把地毯铺上
Stop, Mort, keep that carpet on.
该死  博斯柯探长
Damn it, Sergeant Bosco.
你让大家都染上了你的毒瘾
You're infecting everyone with your poison.
你不是还要去抓那个珠宝店劫匪么
Don't you have a jewelry store thief to catch or something?
我有这东西啊  它叫无线电对讲机
That's why I have one of these; it's called a radio.
还有这个  它叫警枪
And one of these; it's called a gun.
是么  那么这东西你就没有了吧
Yeah, well, what you don't have is one of these.
心
A heart.
很高兴跟你做生意  鲍勃
Pleasure doing business with you, Bob.
这下你未来30年都不用给老妈买礼物了
Wow. Now you won't have to get Mom another gift for 30 years.
是啊  这是有史以来最棒的礼物了
Yup. This is the best present ever,
是活生生的记忆啊
a living memory.
我和你妈妈还在一边刻了名字呢  看
Your Mom and I even carved our initials on the side. See?
-BB是谁  -鲍勃・贝尔彻
- Who's "BB"? - Bob Belcher.
不  另外那个BB
No, who's the other "BB"?
什么另外的...
Uh, what other...
天哪
Oh, God.
-真好玩  -你说啥
- This is fun. - What?
芭芭拉・邦克利
Barbara Bunkley!
我怎么能忘了那年情人节
Oh, how could I have forgotten that Valentine's Day was
是和芭芭拉・邦克利过的呢
with Barbara Bunkley?
芭芭拉・邦克利是谁
Who is Barbara Bunkley?
我到底在想什么  芭芭拉・邦克利
What was I thinking? Barbara Bunkley!
谁能告诉我芭芭拉・邦克利是谁
Will someone please tell me who Barbara Bunkley is?!
我猜她可能是我们的亲生母亲吧
I'm guessing it's our real mom.
而且她又漂亮又擅长运动
And she's beautiful and sporty.
她是我在遇到你们老妈之前的女友
She was my girlfriend the year before I met your mother.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe that.
我记忆中的那次约会居然是跟她过的
The date I'm remembering wasn't with your mom.
真是个白痴
What a moron!
所以这次爱的任务其实是个错误么
So this love mission was a sham?
雨果  这烂玩意儿我不要了
Hugo, I don't want it anymore.
你拿回去吧
Take this stupid thing back.
不好意思  鲍勃  恕不退货
Oh, no, Bob, no refunds.
好了好了  这样就对了
Okay, okay, there we go.
看来我俩都不怎么有女人缘啊
I guess we're a little short on women, huh?
是啊  是啊  关节那边用点力
Yeah, yeah, work those nubs.
没错  就是那儿
Ooh, that's it, right there.
再告诉你们一件事
Another hard truth about me...
你个蠢...
Oh, you stupid...
我用胡椒喷雾剂喷了我的理发师
I pepper-sprayed my barber,
你看这都剪的是啥
but I mean, look at this.
我来说一个
Here it goes.
我每晚都打扮成圣诞老人
I dress up as Santa every night.
只有这样我才能入睡
It's the only way I can go to sleep.
怎样  "十年宫颈炎"小姐
Uh... What, Miss ten-year yeast infection.
我劝你去看医生
See a doctor, why don't you?
我有一个在监狱的笔友
I have a prison pen pal.
他以为我叫米歇尔
He thinks my name is Michelle.
按理说他是我的未婚夫
Technically he's my fianc?
我还撞了特斯塔维德的老婆
I also ran over Vinny Testaverde's wife.
前美国橄榄球员
我受够了
Oh, that's it!
不准任何人再讲自己的丑事了
Everyone needs to stop listening to this cruddy duddy right now!
真可惜  琳达
Too bad, Linda, you just
你根本不懂约会
don't know anything about dating.
谁说我不懂
Yes, I do.
-那为什么大家都听我的  -才没有
- Then why is everyone listening to me? - They're not.
-有  -是么  那没了这个
- They are. - Oh, yeah, well, without this...
就没人会听你的了吧  这位硬汉
...no one's gonna listen to you anymore, tough guy.
琳  我想你不能抢警察的枪
Uh, Lin, I don't think you can take a police officer's gun.
为什么不能  我这不就抢了  看
Sure I can. I just did. Look.
不  我是说  那是违法的
No, I mean, by law.
你到底知不知道自己刚刚做了什么
Do you have any idea what you've just done?
不知道  不太清楚
No. Kind of.
很糟糕吗
Is it bad?
你被逮捕了
You're under arrest.
太紧了  太紧了
Oof, oof, tight. Too tight.
闭嘴  都是均码的
Shush. One size fits all. Shut up.
-发生什么事了  -妈妈被逮捕了
- What's going on? - Mommy's getting arrested.
-啥  -我还以为只是老爸搞砸了
- What? - Whoa-ho-ho, I thought Dad blew it.
是啊  妈妈今天也搞砸得很彻底
Yeah, well, Mommy blew it real bad here today.
-都给她搞砸了  -现在的情况就是
- She blew it. - Oh. What's going on
她犯了抢警员武器的大罪
is taking an officer's sidearm is a felony.
老妈  你居然抢了她的枪
Whoa, Mom, you took his gun?
她确实抢了  露易丝
She sure did, Louise.
我只是想控制下快速约会的局面
I just wanted to get control of speed dating.
控制那样的局面可不需要用到枪
That does not seem like a thing you would need a gun for.
你都去哪儿了  鲍鲍
Where have you been, Bobby?
我们花了一整天
We spent all day helping Dad
帮老爸给你找最完美的情人节礼物
get you the perfect Valentine's gift.
一整天  你们没去学校吗
All day? You kids weren't at school?
那是老爸给我们的奖励
Dad sprung us.
我想在今天为你做点特别的
I wanted to do something special for you today.
我们  我们跑了整个小镇
We... we went all over town trying to find this thing
去找我们第一个情人节玩过的这个东西
from our first Valentine's Day together.
-老爸闯红灯了  -我们去唐人街了
- Dad ran a red light. - We went to Chinatown.
-还有单身汉酒吧  -单身汉酒吧
- And Pickles. - Pickles?
还花500块买了这个
And I spent $500 on it,
可它并不是我们第一个情人节玩过的东西
but it wasn't from our first Valentine's Day together.
是我和芭芭拉・邦克利在情人节玩的东西
It was from a Valentine's Day I spent with Barbara Bunkley.
我记错了
I remembered it wrong.
对不起  我  我真是个白痴
I'm so sorry, I'm... I'm an idiot.
所以你是在告诉我
So you're telling me
你让孩子们翘课跑了大半个小镇
you let the kids play hooky to run all over town
去找一个你错记成我们约会玩过的
to hunt down some expensive thing you remembered
贵得要命的东西
from a date we didn't even go on?
是的
Yes.
那  真是
That... is...
太浪漫了
so romantic!
-什么  -鲍鲍
- What? - Oh, Bobby!
你为我这么大费周折
You went through all that trouble for me.
这是我过的最棒的情人节了
This is the best Valentine's Day ever.
最棒的
Ever!
给我
Give me that.
所以你是来参加快速约会的么
So you came here for speed dating?
不是  一家珠宝店被抢了
No. A jewelry store got robbed.
在这片辖区发现了劫匪的踪影
The suspect was spotted in the area.
-可你留下来参加快速约会了  -是的
- But you stayed for speed dating? - Yeah.
-你肯定是想马子想疯了  -是又怎样
- You must be hard up for chicks.  -Yup.
我居然在情人节被捕了  对不起
I'm sorry I'm getting arrested on Valentine's Day.
来亲一个
Come here.
所以  现在是怎样
So, uh... what,
我要跟你们俩去派出所吗
I'll-I'll follow you two down to the station?
没错  这位女士要马上跟我去...
Yep. This little lady is going right to...
等下  闭嘴  都闭嘴
Shh! Shh! Wait! Shut up! Shut up!
请注意
Be advised.
15大道和格兰德街街口发现嫌犯
Jewelry store suspect spotted at 15th and Grand.
好  我马上过去  你  跟我去
All right, I'm on my way. You, follow me.
今天算你走运
Well, I guess it's your lucky day.
-你在跟我说话吗  -不是  我的天
- You talking to me? - No, for God's sake.
等你回警局
I'll show you how to use the radio
我得教教你怎么用对讲机
when you get back to the station.
给假情报太容易了
It's so easy to call in a false tip.
那两条街根本就不在一起
Those streets don't even intersect.
嗨  蒂娜
Hi, Tina.
-嗨  小吉米  -你今天没来学校
- Hi, Jimmy, Jr. - You weren't at school today,
我给你带作业来了
so I brought you your homework.
-谢谢  -还有情人节贺卡
- Thanks. - And a Valentine's card.
你不打开看看么
Aren't you gonna open it?
是桃心
"Heart"
不是"来自于"了  太好了
not "From." Yes.
那么  明天学校见
So, see you at school tomorrow.
我非常"桃心"[乐意]
I'd really "Heart" That.
啥
Uh, what?
我非常"桃..."
I'd really "Hea..."
-我得走了  -好的  我也是
- I got to get going. - Yeah, me, too.
那个  关于你之前说的事
So, that, uh, stuff you said earlier,
那是你人生中最糟的事么
that's the worst about you?
没错  是那样  不过还有一次
Yup. That's it. Oh, except for one time...
别说了
Oh, oh, oh! Don't say it.
这是我的电话号码
Here's my number.
我凑成一对咯
Hey, I made a match!
我看我铁定会搞砸
I bet I screw this up.
*两个人*
*Two people*
*永远在一起*
*Together forever*
*安稳的生活*
*Security in life*
*有人爱你*
*And someone to love ya*
*不再孤单*
*Instead of being all alone*
*孤独的活着*
*Such a lonely existence*
*两个人*
*Two people*
*永远在一起*
*together forever*
*安稳的生活*
*Security in life*
*有人爱你*
*And someone to love ya*
*不再孤单*
*Instead of being all alone*
*如果要这样孤独的活着*
*Such a lonely existence*
*我宁愿去死*
*I'd kill myself.*
这歌真心酸
Tough song.
在唱我们俩呢  莫特
It's talking about us, Mort.